[TV]　次のニュースは 最近　各地で続発している
Please help save Gon!
「ユーマ」　未確認生物騒動の 続報です。
Use your heads! If you have an idea, take action!
[TV]　今回の騒ぎが　今までのものと 決定的に違う点は
If there's something I can do, tell me.
増え続ける被害者 そして　存在を裏づける
I'll do anything!
お待たせ。 よし　行くか。
Defeat x And x Reunion
あっちは 訳　分かんねえ国　多いからな。
Oh, it's Brother.
でも元は　アリだろ？
Did you sleep well? Uh-huh.
巣の周りで ウロウロしてりゃいいのによ
Where are we?
何で　こんなとこまで…　なぁ？
The hospital. My friend is here, sleeping. He's very sick.
偶然ってことは ないんじゃない？ ＮＧＬにしても 東ゴルトーにしても
I want to help get him
外に情報が ほとんど出ない国でしょ？
on his feet again.
アリからすりゃ 安心して侵略できるってわけか。
You want Something to take over.
お　結構　久しぶり。
Boo! Just when I was able to spend time with you! Don't worry. Like I told you...
変わってねえなぁ。
We'll be together from now on.
ん？
And that's a promise.
爆弾も全く効かないし 対応に苦慮している。
Though I'll have to check whether it's specific to Killua or something
that happens after a wish is used to heal.
どういう意味だ？
Either way, the power to destroy and fix
あっ…。 あっ…。
can become a powerful tool
if the user can be tamed.
アリの仕業か。
His utter lack of humanity and wicked ambition
だが　死者には違いないだろ？ 何が問題なんだ？
deviate even from the path of an assassin.
異形の姿になってな。 彼らを元通りにするすべが あるか否か
How tragic... When he was being controlled, he suffered less.
ホント　変わらねえな。
Alluka is only awake when Something is asleep.
ずれたとこで迷走してやがる。
She spends less time as Alluka than one would think.
俺達は勝手にやるぜ。 邪魔する奴は　倒すだけだ。 安心しな。 今日中に退治してやるよ。
The time after Something's requests
aren't met and people die, until Something makes the next level-1 request...
自称　女王をな。
Or the time when request-making is paused
after someone leaves Something
我は女王なり
before her three requests are complete...
繰り返す　投降せよ 逆らいし者は　極刑に処す 選ばれし者は 楽園への永住を約束しよう
Or the time after Something fixes and falls asleep, until someone else makes a wish
to Alluka and has it granted...
母　最大の失敗は 増兵するのに産卵という
Making this the last wish and never
wishing to Something again
古くて非効率的な方法を とらざるを得なかったこと。
would be the best thing that could happen.
ぐっ…。 あ…。
Hand... Hand...
異議なし。
Please, Something...
今度の連中が　ただ者でないことが 分かりますだ。 常時　野生に身を置きし者の 足運び。
Such incredible power...
強いの？
What's happening inside?
はい。
Who's doing this?
このパイク　ザザン様に 全て　ささげますだ！
What is this?
いってまいります！
I've never felt anything like this before.
さて　私も。
Are you serious? Are you serious?
ご出陣ですね。
Then I'm going to do whatever I want.
ホクロ…　いや　穴？
Magnificent.
ボノレノフは　開発によって すみかを追われた少数部族
belongs to me.
ギュドンドンド族の男子は
Then let me ask the two remaining candidates
３歳の割礼と同時に 体の至る所に針を通す
if they have anything they want to say.
その穴からは 大きさ　形状　動きの強弱で
If not, we will proceed with the final vote.
多様な音を出すことができる
It's futile.
敵部族や猛獣と戦う前には
It doesn't matter what you have to say.
自らの体で戦士の歌を奏で 勇ましく戦う 彼らは 踊る戦士「バプ」と呼ばれる
Well, I have a feeling that
this election is already over, but I would like to ask Leorio-san a question.
鳴らす音色が美しいほど
Can you answer this question for me again?
より高級な精霊が 降りて来ると信じられ
What will you do if you become chairman?
熟練した「バプ」は　神と同格化され 長老以上の発言力を持つ
Leorio-san, can you please
give us your answer again? What will you do if you become chairman?
「バト＝レ・カンタービレ」！
That's all.
一族の血を継ぐ者。
In that case, do you have any
plans for shuffling personnel or restructuring the organization?
精霊と一族の名に懸けて
Of course not!
貴様ごときに遅れはとらない。 今の一撃
I don't even know why I'm
standing here right now!
本当に　一族とやらの 誇りを込めたのか？
Naturally...
だとしたら　ヘヘヘ…！
Those are all the questions I have.
随分と安い魂だな。 撤回は　しなくていい。
It's futile, Pariston. Everyone was aware of those answers
when they voted for Leorio.
しょせん　獣の戯言 俺の心には響かない。
His supporters applauded because they
have every intention of backing him!
うん　１対１なら 相手が　どんなに強かろうが
Do you have any questions for me?
これさえ刺せば 俺の勝ちなんだけど
No! Let's just get this over with! I understand.
あれ　刺さるのかな？ うわっ！
Then I move for an emergency council.
あれを　かい潜りつつ 奴が体をよじった時　生じる
An emergency council.
甲冑への隙間へ アンテナを突き刺す 無傷での成功確率　２０％！
In accordance with the Eighth
and Ninth Hunter Commandments, I move for a vote of confidence. The topic will be a revision of the Hunter
Commandments and the Hunter Exam.
よし　成功。
Hold it right there!
痛っ！ やっぱり無傷じゃ無理だったか。
During the Zodiac council, we decided the Ten Commandments weren't to be touched!
あり？
That isn't relevant right now! No.
何で発動しないのかな？
You're wrong, stupid tiger!
アンテナは ちゃんと刺さってんのに
You're absolutely right.
あんた　操作系だね？
The council reached an 11-1 majority decision.
アンテナをぺルに刺した瞬間 気が緩んだのが　その　いい証拠。
I was the only one in favor of
revising the Ten Commandments.
それが操作能力の 発動条件なんだろう？ うまく行ったと思って 油断したんだ。
If Cheadle-san or Mizaistom-san were
standing on the stage now, I would have deferred to the council and
kept my mouth shut until the election ended.
君も操作系だろ？
But both of them are out of the running.
すでに　別の能力者によって 操作されているから。
And Leorio-san has stated that he
has no plan for the Association! This is the only time
…っていうか リモコン持ってるし 何だ　知ってるの？ そう　操作能力は早い者勝ち。
I can express my opinion as vice chairman,
and not as a member of the Zodiacs. Don't you understand, Kanzai-san?
あとは　あんたを 女王様に連れて行けば ボキの仕事は終了ってこと。
This is the only chance I will ever get!
仕方ないなぁ
Of course, I could use the Eighth Commandment
これ　あんまり 気乗りしないんだけど
to override the council's decision
and force the matter to a vote.
フフフ。
But I wanted to avoid that.
お前のパンチなんぞ 蚊ほども効かんぞ。
The Zodiacs are something precious
that the former chairman left us.
次は何だ？ キックか？　武器か？ 冥土の土産に もう一発だけ打たせてやるぜ。
Hey, if you say something stupid,
he'll pay you back ten times over.
アリのくせに 難しい言葉　知ってんな。
Honestly, part of me wishes to let this
matter die without making waves.
んじゃ　お言葉に甘えて　パンチで。 ヒャハハ！　いいの？　ホントに？
However, the late Teradein-san and
Bushidora-san made an excellent point.
１５ってとこか。
The Third and Fourth Commandments
１５？ ４・５・６…。
are suffering gravely as a result
of the current exam process! He doesn't want to win.
１１・１２・１３・１４
He doesn't want to lose, either. You're right... He's a spiteful person!
１５！ なっ！ 一発　撃っていいんだよな？
He doesn't care about winning or losing, so with nothing to gain or lose, he can
always stay dispassionate and calm, while he manipulates others and plays the rules
まっ　待て！
against us in the worst way possible.
腕を回すほど パンチ力が増大する 「リッパー・サイクロトロン」！
May I say something? Yes, what is it?
何だ　回す数　半分でもよかったな。
If Leorio wins, I volunteer to serve as an advisor. I promise to conduct a comprehensive review of
相変わらず さじ加減が　よく分からん。
the Ten Commandments and
Hunter Exam at that point.
さて　どっちに行くか…。 右か
I won't let you grab any of the Teradein votes!
左か。
I'll counter every point you've made!
コインで決めるか。
To everyone who's voting for
the potential Leorio shows, but who's concerned about
how he will serve initially, I will quell those concerns, even if it
requires me to leave the Zodiacs.
俺って　このままだと どうなるの？
Hey, hey, hey!
奴隷さ 死ぬまで女王様のため働く。 大して　今までの人生と 変わらないだろう。
I have no idea what you people are talking about. But I'm in a hurry to save Gon
as quickly as possible!
アハハ…　ある意味そうだね。
Leorio!
強くは　なるけど 反動が半端ないし
Gon!
ギョギョ。
Damn!
ホッ オナゴのくせに　力あるだな。
You had me so worried!
強靭な糸… 絡め取られたら 逃げるすべは　ない
Leorio!
女王は　どこか。
I'm so glad!
フフフ…　喜びなさい　目の前よ。
So glad!
笑えない冗談ね。 は？　冗談？
Did I l look that bad?
失礼なガキには キツい　お仕置きが必要ね。
Bad doesn't even begin to describe it! Leorio, stop.
嫌だ。 アハハ　フラれた。
Everyone was worried about you.
それじゃ　こっちから行こうかな。
Thank you... Thank you.
はぁ…　僕　急いでるんだけど。
He got us. Pariston wanted Leorio to be his final opponent!
ゲハハ…！　何？　それ。 紙吹雪。
Leorio no longer has the motive or
support to become chairman.
風！
Leorio, you can't tell Gon that Killua healed him.
くっ　アハハ…！
Huh? Why not? You can't tell him!
痛くも　かゆくもないよ！
For Killua's sake, promise not to tell him.
また　紙が…　俺の周りを！
O-Okay, got it. Pariston, when?
無駄っつってんでしょって。 それ。
When did you predict that this would happen? Huh?
何？ これで　いい気になってんの？
No, no... I don't have the ability to predict anything.
やっぱ　ガキだね！
This was pure coincidence.
バカな！　鋼鉄製のロープだぞ。
Please tell me. I want to know.
僕の扇子は紙製だよ。
It hurts to admit this, but I've been defeated.
「蛇咬の舞」！
After he said he would run, I asked a question to provoke him. And he responded that Gon-kun wouldn't die, right?
ぐっ！　ぐあ!!
He isn't going to die.
それ…。 ああ!? 次は　右腕だね。
In that moment, I could see the scene that
just transpired before us.
ん？　傘？
Well, I anticipated Ging-san
and I would stand on stage, and Ging-san would ultimately win.
反応　良し。
First, since Ging-san said Gon-kun wouldn't die, I knew that meant there was a way to heal him.
仕込みの刀 隠すのが好きなの？　坊や。 似た者同士ね。 敵が　ゆったりした服 着てたら
And that if he became part of the
election, I would never win.
何かを隠してる思うの　常識。
Do you understand?
フフフ…。
That was the moment I was defeated.
パイクだ…　パイクの糸で あいつを　がんじがらめにすれば 音は出せねえ
That was all the information you had?
次は　ギタギタにしてやる！
You put your trust in someone
you'd never met before?!
あっ…。
Run for chairman! I'll vote for you!
「ジュピター」！
Get on stage and say something!
うっ…　あっ…　あ!!
Speech! Speech!
虫けらの死にざまに ふさわしいだろ？
Ging?
故郷　流星街に巣くう キメラアントを倒すため 「幻影旅団」の戦いは続く！
This is bad. But, well, this was always gonna happen...